

Pravega Client Library for .NET

September, 9, 2022

FOR

Kaitchuck, Tom Joshi, Sachin Mandalika, Sesh

BY

Sbur, John Lopez, Samuel Cook, Brandon

MENTORED BY

Jillepalli, Ananth

September, 9, 2022

Kaitchuck, Tom Joshi, Sachin Mandalika, Sesh DELL Technologies

Tom Kaitchuck, Sachin Joshi, Sesh Mandalika,

We are excited to be working on your proposed abstract as well as discuss details about approaching development on the Pravega Client Library. This document contains background knowledge of our team including relevant skills, work experience, and education. You will surely learn about us and we are equally excited to learn about you and more details on this project in the near future. Should you have any questions, do not hesitate to email our project lead, John Sbur.

Sincerely, Vegateers









John Sbur

Experience

August 2020-December 2021

Computer Science 121 TA • Washington State University

Taught students C basics such as memory management and

June 2021 - August 2021, May 2022-August 2022

Computer Technician Intern • I-5 Computers

Programmed job ticket management software in WinForms C# using .NET 6.0.
Diagnosed and fixed PC hardware and software.

June 2019 - August 2019

Camp Area Director® Camp Meriwether ® Cascade Pacific Council BSA

Education

Skyview Highschool, Vancouver, WA

Washington State University, Pullman, WA

Major: BS Computer Science

 Cumulative GPU 3.85. Systems Programming, Object Oriented Programming, Automata and Formal Language, Computer Architecture, Software Engineering.

Skills

- C, C#, C++, MIPS Assembly
- Modeling projects in classical and agile models
- UML Diagramming (Use-case diagrams, architectural context diagrams, class diagrams, state-based diagrams, etc.)

Other Interests

- Guitar
- Japanese Language and Culture
- Hiking and High Adventure









Samuel Lopez

Experience

August 2022-December 2023

Computer Science 355 TA • Washington State University

Responsible for tutoring students in functional programming in Haskell, and introductory Python

June 2020 - August 2020

Pharmacy Intern • Fred Meyer

 Responsible for Dispensing up to one hundred medications a day, counseling patients on proper medication usage, administering up to 30 vaccines a day

Jan 2018 - May 2018

Microbiology 101 TA • Washington State University

 Responsible for instructing students on introductory biological techniques, constructed, administered, and graded weekly quizzes.

Education

Washington State University, Pullman, WA Major: BS Computer Science, BS Biochemistry Minor: Math, Software Engineering

Cumulative GPU 3.8. Experience in System Programming, Software Engineering,
Parallel Programming

Skills

- C, C#, C++, Java, Python, Haskell, SQL
- UML Diagrams

Other Interests

- Video Games
- Movies
- Tarantula Keeping











Brandon Cook

Experience

May 2022-August 2022

Software Development Engineer Intern • Amazon Web Services

- Developed a scale testing system for Kubernetes clusters that tested a proprietary Elastic File Systems csi-driver written in Go
- Designed and built a Kubernetes monitoring solution for customers to troubleshoot their issues more effectively

June 2021 - August 2021

Software Engineer Intern • Northeast Integration

- Implemented an organizational system for logging and packing seed packets using Python and Pandas modules extensively
- Worked collaboratively with senior engineers on refactoring and adding code to a bridge monitoring project that tracked wind speeds, radars, shark sensors and other technologies

Education

Washington State University

B.S in Computer Science

Relevant Courses: Systems Programming, Object-Oriented Software Principles, Software Engineering Principles, Programming Language Design, Design and Analysis of Algorithms

Skills

Programming Experience: C, C++, Rust, Go, Python, C#

Libraries/Frameworks: Pandas, NumPy, SciKit-Learn, Kubernetes

Other Interests

- Running/Working out
- Creating technical personal projects